I want him.
Bella, talk to me.
New 30-second spot's ready to roll.
Great.
Cut a few images in of this new guy.
That mug's priceless.
- Eddie, how you trackin'?
- We're hot.
- How hot?
- White hot.
I got "A" team blitzing
chat rooms and blogs.
"B" team's buying ads
and placing the spots.
Site's getting 700 hits per minute.
- Awareness on porn and fight blogs: 92%.
- Bella's got a new 30.
I want you to run that across every sex,
fight and gamer site now.
Hit the gamers hard.
- Got it.
- Push it, people. Push it.
Somewhere, someone on this planet
does not know about this show.
Asia, Africa, Antarctica.
There's a fucking
Eskimo sitting in his little igloo...
who does not know
that we go live in 22 hours.
Find him. Get him. Eddie.
Ninety-two?
I want a hundred.
100% awareness across this Internet.
- You got it?
- You got it.
Did you leave-
No more oranges today.
That's it for the oranges, okay?
Throw it away.
Is that solo ready?
Is it ready?
You know where to put it.
- Hey, pal.
- Hey.
Just so you know, we're fucked.
Oh, yeah. We are screwed.
This show ain't happenin'.
Goldman, come on.
Talk to me.
Where are we at?
I've got 87 cluster-cams
ready and rigged.
I got 147 solos
with all built-in mikes, okay?
I got 60 to 70 all ready
to go out in the field.
- So altogether there's 400 lenses, right?
- Great.
But there are dead spots
all over this island.
I do not have enough time.
This show is not going off.
We are at war, Goldy.
Gotta improvise, overcome, adapt.
This is not war, Breck.
This is television.
It's much more complicated.
I do not have enough hardware...
and if you haven't noticed,
we're in the middle of nowhere.
Mango, do not touch.
What did I say before?
I told you an hour and a half ago.
Do not touch. Thank you.
And on top-Where are you going with that?
Can I have that? Thank you.
Here's the really cool thing.
I got these all-stars.
It's really great,
because between the lot of them...
they all speak three words of English.
So I'm supposed to
run an operation...
that is basically bigger than Farm Aid
meets We Are the World...
and I'm supposed to do it
in sign language?
Are you out of your mind?
Do I look like Quincy Jones?
- Breck.
- You know, it's all gonna work out.
- You know why?
- Why?
'Cause you're the best.
- For the love of Christ.
- Hey, babe.
Donna Sereno just arrived.
Good. She know the score?
Tomorrow morning.
You're her top story.
But be ready.
She's a tough nut.
She's the big dog.
Want the big press,
gotta go to the big dog.
Right. Do it like that.
All right. How do I look?
I'd do ya.
Yeah, but how do I look?
Go get 'em.
Lettuce? Do you want
tomato or anything?
Give me that freakin' sandwich.
Go to work on my satellite.
So, without a major network behind you,
how do you plan to broadcast your show?
The Internet.
I've pulled 10 contestants
from third world prisons.
Each was on death row.
I will free one of them.
See, tomorrow, I'm gonna
bring them here to this island...
where I will give them
a fighting chance at a new life.
It's a fight to the death.
One lives, nine die?
You're airing a live snuff film.
No, Donna.
These contestants were
already dead- condemned.
I'm allowing one to live.
Is that so wrong?
It's immoral and illegal.
You're a multimillionaire who may become
a billionaire producing murder.
I'm done with Hollywood.
I'm going direct to my audience,
worldwide and live.
And my numbers will demolish any show
on any network this year.
Mark my words.
Breck, we have a problem.
I like to think of it
more as a challenge.
We just lost one of our headliners.
What do you mean "lost"?
- They shot my Arab?
- Uh-huh.
We had him on the mainland,
and they shot my fuckin' Arab?
Relax. Relax. Okay.
We got a replacement.
- How'd the interview go?
- Smooth as butter.
Replacement? Who? What? Where?
What have we got?
José Havanando.
Hard-core Guatemalan.
Convicted of 13 torture killings.
He's ready to go.
I don't want a fucking Guatemalan.
I already got two Mexicans.
Look. You see here?
This is the Arab world.
If they don't have anybody to cheer for,
they don't log on.
I want a fucking Arab!
Child-killing, Koran-ranting,
suicide-bombing Arab.
Okay, okay. We're on.
Our scout in Central America...
has got a line
on a 6'7" Islamic fundamentalist.
He's in a joint in El Salvador.
Warden's good to go.
- He's ours if we want him.
- Get him online.
Crew's en route to the prison now.
Has him.
Gringo, the warden wants you now.
Tell the warden to go fuck himself.
What's this all about?
Bullshit.
Can I go now?
Who the hell is this guy?
What have you got, Eddie?
American.
Arrested one year ago
in San Miguel, El Salvador.
Killed three men.
Awaiting death sentence.
Thank you, God.
I thought you wanted an Arab.
Forget the Arab.
I got this guy. He's perfect.
With anti-Americanism
rampant all over the globe...
people are gonna love
to hate this cowboy.
Clean him up.
Let's bring him down.
Get him on a plane.
Come here. Give me the key.
I'll do you a deal. Hey, come back.
Americano, huh?
Big boy.
Gonna cut you like
sazizza, capito?
So where they pull you from?
Put a muzzle in it, boy.
- You're already boring me.
- Who you callin' "boy"?
"Ewan McStarley.
London, England.
Four years, Special Forces.
Three peacekeeping tours
through Africa.
Set fire to a village in Rwanda.
Executed 17 men, raped nine women."
Torture. Mutilation. Good stuff.
You ladies should
get along real good.
What in the fuck is wrong with you?
All in a day's work, Rasta.
Get this top off her.
We're in show business,
not a soup kitchen.
Where's my new guy?
The American.
Right over there.
Hey. I'm lan Breckel.
- I produce television.
- Well, good for you.
Maybe you heard of me.
Bud, I ain't been watchin'
too much TV lately.
Why don't you have a seat?
You and the others
will be taken to an island...
where you'll fight against each other.
If you're the last one
left alive after 30 hours...
I will set you free
with a pocket full of cash.
- How's that sound?
- What's this got to do with TV?
Not TV.
The Internet.
I'll be streaming the entire event
live across the World Wide Web.
Your rap sheet's a little thin.
"Jack Conrad, American.
Blew up a building in El Salvador,
killing three men."
- What were you doing in El Salvador?
- Workin' on my tan.
- Why'd you blow the building up?
- It was blockin' my sun.
- What do you do for a living, Jack?
- I'm an interior decorator.
Okay. I see.
Well, where are you from
back in the States then, huh?
- Alaska.
- Alaska. Whereabouts?
About 80 miles north of Anchorage.
Little fishing town.
You probably heard of it.
It's called Fuck Your Mama.
Babe, do me a favor.
Why don't you write a bio for this redneck.
Let's say he's from Arkansas.
An arsonist, a racist,
a KKK Klansman.
Blew up a Baptist church.
Fugitive from the FBI.
Ended up in Central America...
where he blew up a clinic for retards
and handicapped people, killing dozens.
Women, children, blah, blah.
Do it right now. Get it to Bella.
I don't know who you are,
and I don't care.
But I don't play games.
You don't have to win...
but everybody plays.
Come on.
Hey, boss.
How about something to eat?
Oh, yeah. Husband and wife.
Lovers.
You know, you can stick together,
fight as a team...
but the fact of the matter is, only one
of you will get off the island alive.
Easy. Easy.
Easy.
Hope you can run your feet
as fast as you run your mouth.
Easy, Rosa.
Let's get out of here.
Okay. Listen up, gang.
On your ankle you all have a rig...
packed with 20 ounces
of plastic explosive.
Twenty ounces.
That's enough
to incinerate you, your dog...
and the small house you may be
residing in at the time.
In exactly 30 hours from now...
that plastic explosive
will do what it does best.
You want that rig
removed from your ankle...
simply be the sole survivor
in 30 hours from now.
There are two other ways
to detonate an ankle rig.
One:
You see that red pull tab?
Yank on that,
and after a 10-second delay...
boom.
Two:
Tamper with the rig, you mess with
the wires, you try and pick the lock...
instantly, without delay...
boom.
It's a very simple game.
Kill...
or die.
Choppers are coming.
Cons are on the way. We ready? Goldy?
What, are you kidding me?
Absolutely not.
- Bella?
- Yeah. I was born ready.
- Eddie?
- Good to go.
Bella, give me some
old-school rock and roll.
Goldy, our satellite gonna hold up?
Hey, no.
Bella, cue the music.
Eddie.
Take us live to the Web.
And each of you- dead.
Bite this.
Hey, gringo!
I'll look after your wife!
Okay. Give me 182-B.
That's genius, Goldy.
I tell you, man.
You're the best.
Say that again.
I'll be waiting for
your ass in the bush!
It's going to be a festa!
Breakfast, lunch and dinner!
Okay. You're up. Let's go.
Open up! Open your mouth!
I said open your mouth!
Put that in your mouth!
Get out of here.
- Oops.
- Oops?
That's no "oops."
That's a fuckup times 10.
Give me this.
Hey, idiots. Watch where
you're tossing these guys.
I got a fucking show to put on.
Open up.
Open your mouth.
Come on.
Open your fuckin' mouth.
- Goddamn it!
- He never saw that coming.
You dumb son of a bitch!
Eddie, talk to me.
We got 'em all in a nice little cluster
on the south end of the island.
- Good.
- It's only a matter of time.
- Breck.
- Action. We got action.
Get me in there.
Bella, give me some music.
All right. What have we got?
We're on 23, 24, 31 - all good angles.
We're on 23 now.
This is hard-fucking-core, man!
That's gotta hurt.
She's pulled it.
Sweet!
- That's what I'm talking about, people.
- Nice. Very nice.
Go to 112.
Right! Oh, bam! Five million!
- Listen up. People. Breck.
- What?
Five million users
have just logged on to the site.
Okay. Well, that's a start.
That's a start?
Well, what are you after?
You know how many households
watch the Super Bowl?
- Yeah, like 40 million.
- Right. That's what I'm after.
- Well, that's impossible.
- Yeah, really?
You wait till the blogs and chat rooms...
start hyping the fact that this
right-wing dirt bag just got wasted live...
by a hot African chick
with a nice rack.
Trust me, Goldy.
The Internet- it's wildfire.
Good work.
You trackin' me?
Are you following me?
No, ese.
Partner, you can move on
or things are gonna get a little rough.
Easy, ese.
I'm looking for my wife.
That's all I want.
My Rosa.
Gringo, try this.
This shit is fucked up.
Now that's what I'm talkin' about.
- What's your coverage here?
- Cluster-cam set.
Got three additional cameras
in this location.
Let's spice it up then, huh?
Slice and dice.
Yeah. I'm slicing and dicing.
Do I tell you how to do your job?
Thanks.
Calm down, homey.
Get down.
- Nice.
- I love this Japanese dude.
Come on. Who's your money on?
Who do you like?
Guys, could you please go back to your space,
'cause this is kind of like my space.
Come on, nigga.
Motherfucker!
Lovely day, don't you think?
No, you settle down, son.
Bit lively this morning,
ain't we, tiger?
I saw you fight the spade.
Pretty ballsy for
a little geezer, isn't ya?
The way I see it...
you and me clear some of this scum up
on the island.
Together. A team.
Alliance. You and me.
You understand?
You want these?
They look better on you.
Hold on right there, big man.
Slow down.
Just slow down.
If you stay down,
we don't have a problem.
We have a big fuckin' problem.
Hey, Breck.
Something's going down.
I got two cons right on top
of each other.
It's Conrad and the big dude.
Goldy, what are you, blind?
- What?
- Get this screen up on the live feed.
- Okay. I got it right here.
- Music, Bella. Music.
Now, Bella.
Okay. We're on 202 now.
Zoom in.
208 and 205.
Hold on a minute!
- Hey, Breck.
- Yeah.
Twelve million.
We just hit 12 million subscribers
online right now.
Hey. You hear that, Goldy?
Twelve million.
Yeah. Well, 12 million
still isn't 40 million.
- Still ain't no Super Bowl.
- Not yet.
Bella, Eddie, replay that fall in super slo-mo
until we get something better.
Lan Breckel. Where is he?
What do we know?
He could be streaming the data
to a server from almost anywhere.
I've contacted Interpol.
They're collecting information
from agencies all over the world.
The island is somewhere
in the South Pacific.
I got World War II historians
and regional experts...
examining the images from the Web site.
Between Indonesia and New Guinea
there are, like, 2,000 tiny islands.
Needle in a haystack.
Ten prisoners in this thing.
Two of them are American.
One is Kreston Mackie.
African-American.
He escaped incarceration- 2002.
Ironically, two years later,
ends up on death row in Malaysia.
- What about the other guy?
- I can't find a thing.
It's like he doesn't exist.
I just got a tip on the hotline
about the American, Jack Conrad.
Shoot.
The guy who recognized him on the Internet
says they went to high school together...
only he says
his real name's Jack Riley.
US Army, retired.
Until a year ago, he was living in Texas.
Then he disappeared.
Vanished.
Family, friends-
no one's heard from him since.
He had a girlfriend
named Sarah Cavanaugh.
Divorced, two kids,
works as a waitress.
Gimme the ball!
- Got ya.
- Let go of me!
- No, you!
- Mikey.
Off your brother.
- You two get yourselves cleaned up.
- Hey, come back here!
Dinner in 30.
Hello?
Sarah Cavanaugh?
Yes.
This is Special Agent Wilkins
of the FBI.
I need to ask you a few questions
about Jack Riley.
Hey. You're early.
Mike, can I get on your computer?
- Sure.
- You got high-speed, right?
- Why? What is it?
- It's Jack.
Come on. Come on.
- What's goin' on?
- It's loading.
What do you see? Come on.
What is it?
They want my credit card.
- Okay.
- What you got?
Jack.
- Holy shit. That's Jack.
- Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry.
"KKK member"?
- Hey. What's it say?
- Wait.
What's it say?
"Bombed a clinic for the handicapped
and the mentally retarded"?
- "Fled to El Salvador."
- El Salvador?
It's all lies.
I gotta see this.
Try the live stream.
Paco.
Very romantic.
I can't remember. Did I tell you
how sexy I thought your missus was?
Come on, Mr. Angry.
Speed, baby!
That's what that is!
Come on!
Paco!
Don't you just love it
when that happens?
Calm down. Calm down.
I'll fucking slap you, you keep on.
Just want to be friends.
I didn't want this.
How is that? The knee?
There, there.
You smell that?
That's love.
Love in the air, that is.
You're a lucky man.
That is one fit bird you got there.
Paco!
Rosa!
Easy, son. Easy, easy.
That's no way to treat a lady.
Is it, sweetheart?
Fiery little thing, isn't ya?
Little wildcat.
Have a look at those titties here.
Please, no!
No! Stop!
Rosa!
Fuckin' bitch!
- Paco!
- Watch this, hombre!
- How many angles do we have on this?
- This is all we got.
Well, this coverage is no good.
Eddie.
Where's the live unit?
Not far.
Get 'em over there.
Keep still!
Eddie. Numbers.
We're climbin'.
Around 15 mil.
Stop this.
What?
What? Stop this.
Baby, come on.
She's a killer and a whore.
She's a human being.
Yeah. Who went on a killing spree
with her husband.
They were gonna execute her
in Guatemala. Remember?
No. No. This is wrong.
- This is sick.
- You know what?
The drama- I want it up there.
Not here. Okay? Please.
Lan, how can you let this go on?
It's just happening.
And we're shooting it. It's not my doing.
It is your doing.
You set it up.
I put 10 people out there,
and whatever happens, happens.
Pure reality.
- Yeah.
- No intervention.
Where the hell
do you think you're going?
Fresh air.
What?
You're getting all soft
on me, are you?
I'm gonna hear a crybaby story
from you too?
Or are we just having
a crisis of conscience?
No, Breck. It's not- It's-
It's-
It's not exactly easy to watch.
But I'm with ya.
Eddie, are you with me?
Hell yeah. I love this job.
Bella?
I love what I do.
We're a team, Breck.
Good. You know, Eddie and Bella,
you two give me hope for the future.
That's one angry bitch.
Don't worry about him.
He won't get far.
Amigo, what happened?
Amigo, talk to me.
- What's goin' on?
- I'm gonna kill them.
We've got company.
Just keep it down.
Come on.
You help me to kill them.
Together we could kill them both.
You're not making sense.
They took her like a dog.
They cut her.
And they made me-
You help me to get them.
You help me to-
No, I'll help you stay alive.
Get yourself together.
- Now get up.
- I can't, ese.
My knee is broke.
Calm down.
I don't want to kill you.
I just want to get
this bomb off my leg.
You can trust me.
- He's letting her go?
- For fuck's sake. What is this?
Friendship Island?
How's your knee?
I can't walk.
I can't fight.
I can't do nothing but limp around
with this fucking stick.
You kill them for me.
You kill both of them for me.
Hey, I'm sorry, amigo.
There's something I gotta do.
What you gotta do?
I saw a weather tower
on the north end of the island.
There's gotta be a radio in there.
You call for help?
We're light-years from help, man.
So who you call?
You got a woman...
or a wife?
Yeah.
Something like that.
Drop a Christmas bag to McStarley.
Give him the works.
Send him to the Japanese ruins.
I'll take that.
Think that's got my name on it.